A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, Cox and Reece Investigations FA418
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Washington D. C. Files, 3; 16.32 Cubic Feet 38 letter document boxes, 3 legal document boxes and 2 half-legal boxes
  - J-14-Reece Committee Transcript, Vol. IV, 1954 May 19 (Box 66, Folder 1018)
  - J-14-Reece Committee Transcript, Vol. V, 1954 May 20 (Box 66, Folder 1019)
  - J-14-Reece Committee Transcript,Vol. VI, 1954 May 24 (Box 66, Folder 1020)
  - J-14-Reece Committee Transcript, Vol. VII, 1954 May 25 (Box 66, Folder 1021)
  - J-14-Reece Committee Transcript, Vol. VIII, 1954 May 26 (Box 66, Folder 1022)
  - J-14-Reece Committee Transcript, Vol. IX, 1954 June 2 (Box 66, Folder 1023)
  - J-14-Reece Committee Transcript, Vol. X, 1954 June 3 (Box 66, Folder 1024)
  - J-14-Reece Committee Transcript, Vol. XI, 1954 June 4 (Box 66, Folder 1025)
  - J-14-Reece Committee Transcript, Vol. XII, 1954 June 8 (Box 67, Folder 1026)
  - J-14-Reece Committee Transcript, Vol. XIII, 1954 June 9 (Box 67, Folder 1027)
  - J-14-Reece Committee Transcript, Vol. XIV, 1954 June 15 (Box 67, Folder 1028)
  - J-14-Reece Committee Transcript, Vol. XV, 1954 June 16 (Box 67, Folder 1029)
  - J-14-Reece Committee Transcript, Vol. XVI, 1954 June 17 (Box 67, Folder 1030)
  - J-14A-Transcript of Hearings: Index, 1954 (Box 67, Folder 1031)
  - J-15a-Statement Submitted to Reece Committee: General, 1954 (Box 67, Folder 1032)
  - J-15b-Statement Submitted to Reece Committee: Supplement: Rockefeller Foundation, 1954 (Box 67, Folder 1033)
  - J-15c-Statement Submitted to Reece Committee: Supplement: General Education Board, 1970-1971 (Box 67, Folder 1034)
  - J-15d-Preliminary Draft of Statement Sent to the Trustees, 1954 (Box 68, Folder 1035)
  - J-15e-Source Material, 1950-1954 (Box 68, Folder 1036)
  - J-15f-Willits' Affidavit RE: Kohlberg's Request to Investigate Institute of Pacific Relations and Wormser Correspondence, 1954 (Box 68, Folder 1037)
  - J-15g-Footnote to Appendix A: Supporting Material, 1954 (Box 68, Folder 1038)
  - J-15h-Rhind Memo RE: Requests for Rockefeller Foundation and General Education Board Statement to Reece Committee, 1954 (Box 68, Folder 1039)
  - J-16-Answer to Cox Questionnaire Prepared for Distribution to Reece Committee and Press (Not Used), 1952 (Box 68, Folder 1040)
  - J-17a-Javits Resolution to Investigate the Reece Committee, Congressional Records, 1954 July 20 (Box 68, Folder 1041)
  - J-17b-Javits Correspondence, 1954 (Box 68, Folder 1042)
  - J-17c-Javits Speech, Congressional Record, 1954 August 9 (Box 68, Folder 1043)
  - J-18-Costs of Cox and Reece Investigations, 1954 June 1 (Box 68, Folder 1044)
  - J-19-Keele Article on "Government's Attitude Towards Foundations", 1954 (Box 68, Folder 1045)
  - J-20-Reece Committee Report, 1954-1955 (Box 68, Folder 1046)
  - K-1a (1)-Central Administration: Gregg, 1914-1952 (Box 68, Folder 1047)
  - K-1a (2)-Central Administration: Paine, 1933-1952 (Box 68, Folder 1048)
  - K-1a (3)-Central Administration: Rusk, Rhind and Kimball, 1951-1952 (Box 68, Folder 1049)
  - K-1b-Division of Medicine and Public Health, 1949-1953 (Box 68, Folder 1050)
  - K-1c-Memoranda to Counsel: Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1952 (Box 69, Folder 1051)
  - K-1d-General Education Board, 1952 (Box 69, Folder 1052)
  - K-1e-Humanities, 1964-1967 (Box 69, Folder 1053)
  - K-1f-Reference Service: D. B. Foster, 1952 (Box 69, Folder 1054)
  - K-1g (1)-Social Sciences, 1948-1952 (Box 69, Folder 1055)
  - K-1g (2)-Social Sciences: Evans, 1942-1952 (Box 70, Folder 1056A)
  - K-1g (2)-Social Sciences: Evans, 1942-1952 (Box 70, Folder 1056B)
  - K-1g (2)-Social Sciences: Evans, 1942-1952 (Box 70, Folder 1056C)
  - K-1h-Expenses and Reservations for Washington Hearings, 1952 (Box 70, Folder 1057)
  - K-2-Charge-Out Lists: Doris B. Foster, 1952-1953 (Box 70, Folder 1058A)
  - K-2-Charge-Out Lists: Doris B. Foster, 1952-1953 (Box 70, Folder 1058B)
  - K-3-Miscellaneous Memos, 1952 (Box 70, Folder 1059)
  - K-4-Witness Statements: Duplicates and Drafts, 1952 (Box 71, Folder 1060)
  - K-5-Published Criticisms, 1938-1952 (Box 71, Folder 1061)
  - K-6-Citations, 1938-1954 (Box 71, Folder 1062A)
  - K-6-Citations, 1938-1954 (Box 71, Folder 1062B)
  - L-1a-Central Administration, 1970-1972 (Box 71, Folder 1063)
  - L-1c-Division of Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1954 (Box 71, Folder 1064)
  - L-1d-General Education Board, 1953-1954 (Box 71, Folder 1065)
  - L-1e-Humanities, 1952-1971 (Box 71, Folder 1066)
  - L-1f-Reference Service, 1952-1954 (Box 72, Folder 1067)
  - L-1g (1)-Social Sciences: Roger F. Evans, 1953-1959 (Box 72, Folder 1068)
  - L-1g (2)-Social Sciences: Joseph H. Willits, 1954 (Box 72, Folder 1069)
  - L-1g (2)-Division of Social Sciences: Miscellaneous and Memorandum # 1-15 (Willits), 1954 (Box 72, Folder 1070)
  - L-1g (2)-Division of Social Sciences: Memorandum # 16-32 (Willits), 1954 (Box 72, Folder 1071)
  - L-1g (3)-Division of Social Sciences: Leland C. DeVinney, 1954 (Box 73, Folder 1072)
  - RF, 1913 (Box 73, Folder 1073)
  - RF, 1918 (Box 73, Folder 1074)
  - RF, 1923 (Box 73, Folder 1075)
  - RF, 1928 (Box 73, Folder 1076)
  - RF, 1933 (Box 73, Folder 1077)
  - RF, 1943 (Box 73, Folder 1078)
  - RF, 1948 (Box 73, Folder 1079)
  - RF, 1953 (Box 73, Folder 1080)
  - GEB 1903-1953: Worksheets 1954, 1903-1954 (Box 73, Folder 1081)
  - GEB, 1903 (Box 73, Folder 1082)
  - GEB, 1908 (Box 73, Folder 1083)
  - GEB, 1913 (Box 73, Folder 1084)
  - GEB, 1918 (Box 73, Folder 1085)
  - GEB, 1923 (Box 73, Folder 1086)
  - GEB, 1928 (Box 73, Folder 1087)
  - GEB, 1933 (Box 73, Folder 1088)
  - GEB, 1938 (Box 73, Folder 1089)
  - GEB, 1943 (Box 73, Folder 1090)
  - GEB, 1967-1968 (Box 73, Folder 1091)
  - GEB, 1953 (Box 73, Folder 1092)
  - Work Sheets-Financial Corrections, Reece Committee Report, 1954 (Box 73, Folder 1093)
  - Work Sheets-Investigation, Reece Committee Report, 1954 (Box 74, Folder 1094)
  - A-1-General Education Board: Charter and By-Laws, 1954 (Box 74, Folder 1095)
  - A-2-General Education Board: Letters from Commissioner of Internal Revenue RE: Tax Exemption, 1918-1938 (Box 74, Folder 1096)
  - A-3-General Education Board: Officers, 1952-1954 (Box 74, Folder 1097)
  - A-3A-General Education Board: List of Present Trustees and Principal Officers, 1902-1954 (Box 74, Folder 1098)
  - A-3A-General Education Board Trustees and Officers by Years, 1929-1955 (Box 74, Folder 1099)
  - A-3B-Trustees and Principal Officers of the General Education Board, 1954 (Box 74, Folder 1100)
  - A-3B-General Education Board Trustees and Principal Officers, 1902-1954 (Box 74, Folder 1101)
  - A-3C-General Education Board: Officers and Trustees: Interlocking Directories and Published Criticisms, 1948-1954 (Box 74, Folder 1102)
  - A-3D-General Education Board: List of All Persons Who Have Served as Trustees Since Incorporated in 1903, 1954 (Box 74, Folder 1103)
  - A-5-Rockefeller Foundation: List of Present Trustees and Principal Officers, 1913-1954 (Box 75, Folder 1104)
  - A-5-Securities Held, 1902-1954 (Box 75, Folder 1105)
  - A-5b-Trustees and Principal Officers of the Rockefeller Foundation, 1954 (Box 75, Folder 1106)
  - A-5c-Rockefeller Foundation: List of All Persons Who Have Served as Trustees Since Incorporation in 1913, 1954 (Box 75, Folder 1107)
  - A-6-General Educations Board: Finance Committees, Treasurers and Comptrollers, 1902-1954 (Box 75, Folder 1108)
  - A-7A-General Educations Board: Treasurer's Reports, 1951-1953 (Box 75, Folder 1109)
  - A-8-Brief History of General Education Board, 1902-1953 (Box 75, Folder 1110)
  - A-9-General Educations Board: Period of Service of Trustees, Chairmen and Presidents, 1902-1954 (Box 75, Folder 1111)
  - B-1- General Educations Board: Purpose and Program Leaflet, 1952 (Box 75, Folder 1112)
  - B-2-General Education Board: Policies (Box 75, Folder 1113)
  - B-3-General Education Board: Advisory Committees, 1936-1955 (Box 75, Folder 1114)
  - B-4-General Education Board: Operating Procedures with Exhibits A-E, 1951-1952 (Box 75, Folder 1115)
  - B-5-General Education Board: Policy RE: Announcement of Grants (Box 75, Folder 1116)
  - B-6-General Education Board: Statement on Declinations from Rusk, Letter to Dodd, 1954 (Box 75, Folder 1117)
  - B-7-General Education Board: Meetings of Trustees, 1902-1954 (Box 75, Folder 1118)
  - B-7A-General Education Board: Trustee Attendance at Meetings, 1949-1954 (Box 75, Folder 1119)
  - B-7B-General Education Board: Executive Committee Meetings, 1954 (Box 75, Folder 1120)
  - B-7C-General Education Board: Special Trustees Committees, 1953 (Box 75, Folder 1121)
  - B-8-General Education Board: List of Publications, 1947-1951 (Box 75, Folder 1122)
  - B-9-Liberalization Policy on General Education Board Grants with Actions, 1931-1952 (Box 75, Folder 1123)
  - B-10-General Education Board: Memo RE: Declinations, 1936-1954 (Box 75, Folder 1124)
  - C-1a-o-General Education Board: Financial Statements and Schedules of Grants, 1902-1954 (Box 75, Folder 1125)
  - C-2-Books Published as Result of General Education Board Grants, 1916-1951 (Box 75, Folder 1126)
  - C-3-General Education Board: Fellowship Directory, 1922-1950 (Box 76, Folder 1127)
  - C-3A-General Education Board: Fellowship Directory Supplement, 1953-1954 (Box 76, Folder 1128)
  - C-4-General Education Board: Outstanding Fellows with Addenda, 1954 (Box 76, Folder 1129)
  - C-5-Number of Institutions per State Aided by Rockefeller Foundation and General Education Board (Box 76, Folder 1130)
  - C-6- General Education Board: Grants Made During Presidency of Rusk, 1952 July 1-1954 May 31 (Box 76, Folder 1131)
  - C-7a-General Education Board: Actions Concerning the American Council of Learned Societies, American Council on Education, 1921-1954, 1947-1957 (Box 76, Folder 1132)
  - C-7b-General Education Board: Actions Concerning the National Education Association, National Research Council, Progressive Education Association, Social Science Research Council, 1917-1954 (Box 76, Folder 1133)
  - C-8-General Education Board: Matching Grants, 1954 (Box 77, Folder 1134)
  - C-9-General Education Board: Grants to the University of Chicago, 1952 (Box 77, Folder 1135)
  - C-10-General Education Board (Box 77, Folder 1136)
  - C-11-General Education Board-Grants for Work in Foreign Countries (Rockefeller Foundation and General Education Board) (Box 77, Folder 1137)
  - D-1-General Education Board: Summary of House Un-American Activites Committee Citations - General Education Board Grantees, 1935-1952 (Box 77, Folder 1138)
  - D-2-General Education Board: Evaluation of Persons in Answer to Cox Questionnaire (Box 77, Folder 1139)
  - E-1-The General Education Board and Negro Education, 1952 (Box 77, Folder 1140)
  - E-3-General Education Board: A Modern School: Flexner, 1923 (Box 77, Folder 1141)
  - E-3A-General Education Board: "Changes Needed in American Secondary Education" - Eliot, 1924 (Box 77, Folder 1142)
  - E-4-General Education Board: The Problem in General Education, 1943-1954 (Box 77, Folder 1143)
  - E-5-General Education Board: Emergency Education Program, 1933-1936 (Box 77, Folder 1144)
  - H-1a-General Education Board: The Turning of the Tides: Shafer and Snow (Box 77, Folder 1145)
  - I-1-General Education Board: Memorandum RE: Investigation, July to Barnard, 1951 (Box 77, Folder 1146)
  - I-2-General Education Board: Questionnaire and Cox Letter of Transmittal, 1952 (Box 77, Folder 1147)
  - I-3-General Education Board: Answer to Questionnaire, 1952-1954 (Box 77, Folder 1148)
  - I-3A-General Education Board: Exhibits to Questionnaire, 1954 (Box 77, Folder 1149)
  - I-4a-General Education Board: Cox Committee, 1952 (Box 77, Folder 1150)
  - I-4b-General Education Board: Correspondence: Trustees, 1952-1953 (Box 77, Folder 1151)
  - J-1-General Education Board: Dodd Letter, 1953 December 3 Asking Data on Grants, 1953 (Box 77, Folder 1152)
  - J-1A-General Education Board: Report to Committee with Breakdown on "Self-Administered Grants", 1903-1954 (Box 77, Folder 1153A)
  - J-1A-General Education Board: Report to Committee with Breakdown on "Self-Administered Grants", 1903-1954 (Box 77, Folder 1153B)
  - J-2-General Education Board: Rusk Letter to Wormser RE: Origin of Grants (Box 78, Folder 1154)
  - J-2A-General Education Board: Memos Dealing with Origin of Grants, 1954 (Box 78, Folder 1155)
  - J-3a-General Education Board: General Correspondence with Committee (Box 78, Folder 1156)
  - J-4-General Education Board: Statement to Reece Committee and General Education Board Supplement (Box 78, Folder 1157)
  - J-5A-General Education Board: Answer to Cox Questionnaire Prepared for Distribution to Reece Committee and Press (Not Used), 1952 (Box 78, Folder 1158)
  - AAA-1-Bunche, Ralph, 1956-1959 (Box 78, Folder 1159)
  - AAA-2-Reece Committee Report: Analysis (Box 78, Folder 1160)
  - AAA-2, 1954-1959 (Box 78, Folder 1161)
  - AAA-2-I. The Creation & Function of the Committee (p. 1-2), 1953-1954 (Box 78, Folder 1162)
  - AAA-2-II. The Approach of the Committee (p. 2-4), 1953-1954 (Box 78, Folder 1163)
  - AAA-2-III. Foundations and Taxes (p. 4-13) (Box 78, Folder 1164)
  - AAA-2-IV. Statistical Material (p. 13-14) (Box 78, Folder 1165)
  - AAA-2-V. Prefatory Notes & Summary of Findings (p. 15-19) (Box 78, Folder 1166)
  - AAA-2-VI. The Power of the Large Foundation (p. 19-38) (Box 78, Folder 1167)
  - AAA-2-VII. The Concentration of Power-Interlock (p. 39-60), 1952-1954 (Box 78, Folder 1168)
  - AAA-2-VIII. The Foundations and Research in the Social Sciences (p. 60-95), 1954 (Box 78, Folder 1169)
  - AAA-2-IX. The Politcal Activities of Foundations (Box 78, Folder 1170)
  - AAA-2-X. The Foundations and Education (p. 134-168) (Box 79, Folder 1171)
  - AAA-2-XI. Internationalism & the Effect of Foundation Power on Foreign Policy (p. 168-195) (Box 79, Folder 1172)
  - AAA-2-XII. Communism and Subversion (p. 196-206) (Box 79, Folder 1173)
  - AAA-2-XIII. Supplemental Comments (p. 207-212) (Box 79, Folder 1174)
  - AAA-2-XIV. Special Recommendations Not Fully Covered in the Previous Text (p. 212-222) (Box 79, Folder 1175)
  - AAA-2-Statement of B. Carroll Reece (p. 223-226) (Box 79, Folder 1176)
  - AAA-2-Appendix to the Report (p. 227-416) (Box 79, Folder 1177)
  - AAA-2-Minority Views (p. 417-432) (Box 79, Folder 1178)
  - AAA-2-Varney Article (American Legion Magazine), 1955 June (Box 79, Folder 1179)
  - AAA-2-Investigation Notes & Notes on Summer Work, 1954 (Box 79, Folder 1180)
  - AAA-2-The Rockefeller Foundation Annual Report, 1913-1914 (Box 79, Folder 1881)
  - AAA-2-The Rockefeller Foundation Annual Report, 1918 (Box 79, Folder 1182)
  - AAA-2-The Rockefeller Foundation Annual Report, 1923 (Box 79, Folder 1183)
  - AAA-2-The Rockefeller Foundation Annual Report, 1928 (Box 80, Folder 1184)
  - AAA-2-The Rockefeller Foundation Annual Report, 1933 (Box 80, Folder 1185)
  - AAA-2-The Rockefeller Foundation Annual Report, 1938 (Box 80, Folder 1186)
  - AAA-2-The Rockefeller Foundation Annual Report, 1943 (Box 80, Folder 1187)
  - AAA-2-The Rockefeller Foundation Annual Report, 1948 (Box 81, Folder 1188)
  - AAA-2-Tax-Exempt Foundations, Hearings before the Select Committee to Investigate Tax-Exempt Foundations and Comparable Organizations, House Resolution 561, 1952 November 18-21; 24-25; 1952 December 2-3; 8-11; 15; 17; 22-23; November 30. 1952 (Box 81, Folder 1189)
  - AAA-3-Memos to Counsel, 1955 (Box 81, Folder 1190)
  - AAA-4-Institute of Pacific Relations, 1954-1960 (Box 81, Folder 1191)
- Background Information and Miscellaneous, 4; 5.79 Cubic Feet 5 letter document boxes, 1 legal document box, 1 half-legal box, 4 card file boxes (3x5) and 2 record storage boxes
  Primarily consists of financial information and index cards.
  - Documents of Record: D. R. 545-K. Filing Procedure, 1939-1954 (Box 81, Folder 1192)
  - Documents of Record: D. R. 717-803, 1949-1953 (Box 81, Folder 1193)
  - Documents of Record: D. R. 804-Financial Report, 1964-1965 (Box 81, Folder 1194)
  - Documents of Record: D. R. 805-Report on Examination, 1952 (Box 81, Folder 1195)
  - Documents of Record: D. R. 806-820, 1953-1954 (Box 81, Folder 1196)
  - Documents of Record: D. R. 821-Financial Report, 1953 (Box 81, Folder 1197)
  - Documents of Record: D. R. 822-Report on Examination, 1953 (Box 81, Folder 1198)
  - Documents of Record: D. R. 823-851, 1954-1956 (Box 81, Folder 1199)
  - Documents of Record: D. R. 852-Financial Report, 1955 (Box 82, Folder 1200)
  - Documents of Record: D. R. 853-Accountant's Report, 1955 (Box 82, Folder 1201)
  - Documents of Record: D. R. 854-870, 1956-1957 (Box 82, Folder 1202)
  - Documents of Record: D. R. 871-Financial Report, 1956 (Box 82, Folder 1203)
  - Documents of Record: D. R. 872-Accountant's Report, 1956 (Box 82, Folder 1204)
  - Documents of Record: D. R. 873-885, 1957-1958 (Box 82, Folder 1205)
  - Documents of Record: D. R. 886-Financial Report, 1957 (Box 82, Folder 1206)
  - Documents of Record: D. R. 887-Accountant's Report, 1957 (Box 82, Folder 1207)
  - Documents of Record: D. R. 888-895, 1958 (Box 82, Folder 1208)
  - Documents of Record: D. R. 896-Five Years of the Rockefeller Foundation, 1952-1958 (Box 82, Folder 1209)
  - Documents of Record: D. R. 897-898, 1959 (Box 82, Folder 1210)
  - Documents of Record: D. R. 899, Financial Report, 1958 (Box 82, Folder 1211)
  - Documents of Record: D. R. 900-924, 1958-1960 (Box 82, Folder 1212)
  - Documents of Record: D. R. 925-Financial Report, 1959 (Box 82, Folder 1213)
  - Documents of Record: D. R. 926-939, 1959-1961 (Box 82, Folder 1214)
  - Documents of Record: D. R. 940-Financial Report, 1960 (Box 83, Folder 1215)
  - Documents of Record: D. R. 941-955, 1960-1962 (Box 83, Folder 1216)
  - Documents of Record: D. R. 956-Financial Report, 1961 (Box 83, Folder 1217)
  - Documents of Record: D. R. 957-970, 1961-1963 (Box 83, Folder 1218)
  - Documents of Record: D. R. 971-Financial Report, 1962 (Box 83, Folder 1219)
  - Documents of Record: D. R. 972-983, 1962-1963 (Box 83, Folder 1220)
  - Documents of Record: D. R. 984-Schedule of Authorizations, 1964 (Box 83, Folder 1221)
  - Documents of Record: D. R. 985-Financial Statements, 1963 (Box 83, Folder 1222)
  - Documents of Record: D. R. 986-1007, 1963-1965 (Box 83, Folder 1223)
  - Documents of Record: D. R. 1008-Financial Report, 1964 (Box 83, Folder 1224)
  - Documents of Record: D. R. 1009-1031, 1964-1966 (Box 83, Folder 1225)
  - Documents of Record: D. R. 1032-Financial Report, 1965 (Box 83, Folder 1226)
  - Documents of Record: D. R. 1033-1048, 1965-1966 (Box 84, Folder 1227)
  - Documents of Record: D. R. 1049-Financial Report, 1938 April (Box 84, Folder 1228)
  - Documents of Record: D. R. 1050-1066, 1966-1968 (Box 84, Folder 1229)
  - Documents of Record: D. R. 1067-Financial Report, 1967 (Box 84, Folder 1230)
  - Documents of Record: D. R. 1068-1082, 1967-1968 (Box 84, Folder 1231)
  - Documents of Record: D. R. 1083-Financial Report, 1968 (Box 84, Folder 1232)
  - Documents of Record: D. R. 1084-1099, 1968-1970 (Box 84, Folder 1233)
  - Documents of Record: D. R. 1100-Financial Report, 1969 (Box 84, Folder 1234)
  - Documents of Record: D. R. 1101-1107, 1969-1970 (Box 84, Folder 1235)
  - Out-of-Town Vault, List of Contents, 1969 (Box 84, Folder 1236)
  - Treasurer's Office, 1913-1969 (Box 84, Folder 1237)
  - 990A, 1967 (Box 84, Folder 1238)
  - 990A, 1968 (Box 84, Folder 1239)
  - 990A, 1969 (Box 85, Folder 1240)
  - Corporate Administrative Documents, 1964-1966 (Box 85, Folder 1241)
  - Trial Balance, Summary of Appropriations and Expenditures-Appropriations for Allocation and Release, 1969 May (Box 85, Folder 1242)
  - Trial Balance, Humanities & Social Sciences, 1969 May (Box 85, Folder 1243)
  - GEB A: Appropriations Accounts, 1963 (Box 85, Folder 1244)
  - GEB B: Corporate Administration Documents, 1929-1965 (Box 85, Folder 1245)
  - GEB C: Counsel Opinions, 1953-1969 (Box 85, Folder 1246)
  - GEB D: Documents of Record, D. R. 211A-914, 1918-1969 (Box 86, Folder 1247)
  - GEB D: Documents of Record, D. R. 915-936, 1954-1957 (Box 86, Folder 1248)
  - GEB D: Documents of Record, D. R. 937-958, 1958-1962 (Box 86, Folder 1249)
  - GEB E: Fellowship and Scholarship Records, 1950-1954 (Box 86, Folder 1250)
  - GEB F: D. R. 959-972, 1963-1966 (Box 86, Folder 1251)
  - GEB G: Personnel Records, 1950-1959 (Box 86, Folder 1252)
  - GEB H: Publications, 1951 (Box 86, Folder 1253)
  - GEB I: Treasurer's Records, 1962-1963 (Box 86, Folder 1254)
  - GEB J: Select Committee to Investigate Foundations and Other Organizations: Report, 1954 (Box 86, Folder 1255)
  - General Education Board: Document Record 911: Out-of-Town Vault, 1952-1953 (Box 87, Folder 1256)
  - General Education Board Retirement Plan, 1951 (Box 87, Folder 1257)
  - General Education Board Tax Exemption Documents, 1930-1959 (Box 87, Folder 1258)
  - Cox and Reece Investigations, Index to Files (Incomplete) (Box 87, Folder 1259)
  - Personnel and Financial material (Box 88, Box 89)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Restricted from access.
  - Index Cards - A-B (Box 1)
  - Index Cards - C-H (Box 2)
  - Index Cards - I-P (Box 3)
  - Index Cards - Q-Z (Box 4)